<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Signature>
	<Separator>--</Separator>
	<Name>Bryan Johns</Name>
	<NickName>K4GDW</NickName>
	<OtherInfo></OtherInfo>
	<Email>bjohns@greendragonweb.com</Email>
	<Phone></Phone>
	<WebPage>http://www.greendragonweb.com</WebPage>
	<Disclaimer>This electronic mail transmission may contain legally privileged and/or confidential information. This message and/or any files transmitted with it are intended solely for the use of the addressee(s). This communication is to be treated as confidential and the information in it may not be used or disclosed except for the purpose for which it was sent. If you have reason to believe you are not the intended recipient of this communication or have received this e-mail in error please (1) advise me immediately, (2) deleted it and any attached files transmitted from your system, (3) destroy any hard copies of it. You are hereby notified that disclosing, copying, distributing, or taking any action on the contents, attachments, or information herein is strictly prohibited.</Disclaimer>
	<Quotes>
		<Quote>"First they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they attack you, and then you win!" --Ghandi</Quote>
		<Quote>"Those gentlemen, who will be elected senators, will fix themselves in the federal town, and become citizens of that town more than of your state." --George Mason (http://PatriotPost.US/fqd/)</Quote>
		<Quote>"If you can keep your wits about you while all others are losing theirs and blaming you... The world will be yours and everything in it, what's more, you'll be a man, my son." --Rudyard Kipling</Quote>
		<Quote>"When you were born, you cried and the world rejoiced. Live your life so that when you die, the world cries and you rejoice."  --Cherokee Expression</Quote>
		<Quote>"We should invade their countries, kill their leaders and convert them to Christianity." --Ann Coulter, September 13, 2001</Quote>
		<Quote>"Who is more irrational? A man who believes in a God he doesn't see, or a man who's offended by a God he doesn't believe in?" --Brad Stine</Quote>
		<Quote>"...whatever power you give the State to do things FOR you carries with it the equivalent power to do things TO you." --Albert Jay Noc</Quote>
		<Quote>"One can pay back the loan of gold, but one dies forever in debt to those who are kind." --Malayan Proverb</Quote>
		<Quote>"What experience and history teach is this:  that people and governments never have learned anything from history, or acted on principles deduced from it." --Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel</Quote>
		<Quote>"There is a terrible lot of us who don't think that we come from a monkey, but if there are some people who think that they do, why, it's not our business to rob them of what little pleasure they might get out of imagining it." --Will Rogers</Quote>
		<Quote>"The shortest and surest way to live with honor in the world is to be in reality what we would appear to be." --Socrates</Quote>
		<Quote>"It is dangerous to be right in matters on which the established authorities are wrong." --Voltaire</Quote>
		<Quote>"An armed society is a polite society. Manners are good when one may have to back up his acts with his life." --Robert Heinlein</Quote>
		<Quote>"The unforgivable crime is soft hitting. Do not hit at all if it can be avoided; but never hit softly." --Theodore Roosevelt</Quote>
		<Quote>"If ye love wealth better than liberty, the tranquility of servitude than the animating contest of freedom, go from us in peace. We ask not your counsels or arms.  Crouch down and lick the hands which feed you. May your chains sit lightly upon you, and may posterity forget that ye were our countrymen!" --Samuel Adams</Quote>
		<Quote>"Is life so dear or peace so sweet as to be purchased at the price of chains and slavery? Forbid it, Almighty God! I know not what course others may take, but as for me, give me liberty or give me death!" --Patrick Henry</Quote>
		<Quote>"Government's view of the economy could be summed up in a few short phrases: If it moves, tax it. If it keeps moving, regulate it. And if it stops moving, subsidize it." --Ronald Reagan</Quote>
		<Quote>
			while(!Caffeine == null) {
			WriteCode();
			}
		</Quote>
		<Quote>"It's as easy as 01 10 11."</Quote>
		<Quote>"There are 10 kinds of people in the world.  Those who understand binary and those who don't."</Quote>
		<Quote>"Do not meddle in the affairs of Dragons, for you are crunchy  and taste good with ketchup!"</Quote>
		<Quote>"Justice is a certain rectitude of mind whereby a man does what  he ought to do in circumstances confronting him." --St. Thomas  Aquinas</Quote>
		<Quote>"The things that will destroy America are prosperity-at-any-price, peace-at-any-price, safety-first instead of duty-first, the love of soft living, and the get-rich-quick theory of life." --Theodore Roosevelt</Quote>
		<Quote>"True patriotism sometimes requires of men to act exactly contrary, at one period, to that which it does at another, and the motive which impels them---the desire to do right---is precisely the same." --Robert E. Lee</Quote>
		<Quote>"While the people are virtuous they cannot be subdued; but when  once they lose their virtue then will be ready to surrender their liberties to the first external or internal invader." --Samuel Adams</Quote>
		<Quote>"The Key, the whole Key, and nothing but the Key... so help me Codd"</Quote>
		<Quote>"...income redistribution is simply a legal version of what a thief does --  namely, take the rightful property of one person for the benefit of another.  The primary distinction between this behavior and that of Congress is legality." --Walter Williams</Quote>
		<Quote>"Lord, help me to remember that nothing will happen to me today that you  and I together cannot handle."</Quote>
		<Quote>"The Constitution was made to guard the people against the dangers of good intentions." --Daniel Webster </Quote>
		<Quote>"Most powerful is he who has himself in his own power."  --Lucius Annaeus Seneca</Quote>
		<Quote>"To know what you prefer instead of humbly saying 'Amen' to what the world  tells you you ought to prefer, is to have kept your soul alive."  --Robert Louis Stevenso</Quote>
		<Quote>"Beware lest you lose the substance by grasping at the shadow." --Aesop</Quote>
		<Quote>"How much easier it is to be critical than to be correct."  --Benjamin Disraeli</Quote>
		<Quote>"The right of the citizens to keep and bear arms has justly been considered as the palladium of the liberties of a republic..."  --Justice Joseph Story</Quote>
		<Quote>"Let's begin at the beginning. God is the center of our lives; the human family stands at the center of society; and our greatest hope for the future is in the faces of our children." --Ronald Reagan</Quote>
		<Quote>"If a man does not keep pace with his companions, perhaps it is because he hears a different drummer. Let him step to the music which he hears, however measured or far away." --Henry David Thoreau</Quote>
		<Quote>"And then she understood the devilish cunning of the enemies' plan. By mixing a little truth with it they had made their lie far stronger." --C. S. Lewis</Quote>
		<Quote>"Just because you do not take an interest in politics doesn't mean politics won't take an interest in you." --Pericles</Quote>
		<Quote>"Understanding is the reward of faith. Therefore seek not to understand that you may believe, but believe that you may understand." --Augustine</Quote>
		<Quote>"Many law professors, and others who hold contempt for our Constitution, preach that the Constitution is a living document. Saying that the Constitution is a living document is the same as saying we don't have a Constitution. For rules to mean anything, they must be fixed. How many people would like to play me in poker and have the rules be 'living'? Depending on 'evolving standards,' maybe my two pair could  beat your flush." --Walter Williams</Quote>
		<Quote>"Government does not tax to get the money it needs; government always finds a need for the money it gets." --Ronald Reagan</Quote>
		<Quote>"In general, the art of government consists in taking as much money as possible from one party of the citizens to give to the other." --Voltaire</Quote>
		<Quote>"When the people find they can vote themselves money, that will herald the end of the republic." --Benjamin Franklin</Quote>
		<Quote>"We contend that for a nation to try to tax itself into prosperity is like a man standing in a bucket and trying to lift himself up by the handle." --Winston Churchill</Quote>
		<Quote>"The way to crush the bourgeoisie is to grind them between the millstones of taxation and inflation." --Vladimir Lenin</Quote>
		<Quote>"The only difference between a tax man and a taxidermist is that the taxidermist leaves the skin." --Mark Twain</Quote>
		<Quote>"The Declaration of Independence, the words that launched our nation -- 1,300 words. The Bible, the word of God -- 773,000 words. The Tax Code, the  words of politicians -- 7,000,000 words -- and growing!" --Steve Forbes</Quote>
		<Quote>"To consider the judges as the ultimate arbiters of all constitutional questions (is) a very dangerous doctrine indeed, and one which would place us under the despotism of an oligarchy."  -- Thomas Jefferson</Quote>
		<Quote>"Imagination is more important than knowledge.  Knowledge is limited, while imagination encircles the world." -- Albert Einstein 1929</Quote>
		<Quote>"There is no limit to what you can accomplish if you don't care who gets the credit." --Ronald Reagan</Quote>
		<Quote>"Public affairs go on pretty much as usual: perpetual chicanery and rather more personal abuse than there used to be...." --John Adams</Quote>
		<Quote>"The Court is most vulnerable and comes nearest to illegitimacy when it deals with judge-made constitutional law having little or no cognizable  roots in the language or design of the Constitution." --Byron White</Quote>
		<Quote>"Public life is a situation of power and energy; he trespasses against his duty who sleeps over his watch, as well as he that goes over to the enemy." --Edmund Burke</Quote>
		<Quote>"To be prepared for war, is one of the most effectual means of preserving peace." --George Washington</Quote>
		<Quote>"One of the penalties for refusing to participate in politics is that you end up being governed by your inferiors." --Plato</Quote>
		<Quote>"When people stop believing in God, they don't believe in nothing -- they believe in anything."  --G. K. Chesterton</Quote>
		<Quote>"Democracy is a device that ensures we shall be governed no better than  we deserve." --George Bernard Shaw</Quote>
		<Quote>"We hang the petty thieves and appoint the great ones to public office." --Aesop</Quote>
		<Quote>"Under every stone lurks a politician." --Aristophanes</Quote>
		<Quote>"The higher type of man clings to virtue, the lower type of man clings to material comfort.  The higher type of man cherishes justice, the lower type of man cherishes the hope of favors to be received." --Confucius</Quote>
		<Quote>"Little progress can be made by merely attempting to repress what is evil; our great hope lies in developing what is good." --Calvin Coolidge</Quote>
		<Quote>"We must respect the other fellow's religion, but only in the sense and to the extent that we respect his theory that his wife is beautiful and his children smart." --Henry Louis Mencken (1880-1956)</Quote>
		<Quote>"Conservatives saw the savagery of 9/11 in the attacks and prepared for war; liberals saw the savagery of the 9/11 attacks and wanted to prepare indictments and offer therapy and understanding for our attackers." --Karl Rove </Quote>
		<Quote>"Those on the far left are employing the same kind of rhetoric and tactics that worked during the Vietnam War -- where overheated rhetoric and the most vile slander are acceptable if they tarnish the president and hurt our war effort. They have no shame. They play politics like the Islamo-fascists conduct warfare -- dirty, ruthless and reckless, with no discernible rules, no regard for fact and no compunction about stabbing people in the back." --Oliver North</Quote>
		<Quote>"Do your duty in all things. You cannot do more. You should never wish to do less." --Robert E. Lee</Quote>
		<Quote>"Bring your desires down to your present means. Increase them only when your increased means permit." --Aristotle</Quote>
		<Quote>And he said unto them, Cast the net on the right side of the ship, and ye shall find. They cast therefore, and now they were not able to draw it for the multitude of fishes. --John 21:6</Quote>
		<Quote>"I know no safe depository of the ultimate powers of the society but the people themselves; and if we think them not enlightened enough to exercise their control with a wholesome discretion, the remedy is not to take it from them, but to inform their discretion by education." --Thomas Jefferson</Quote>
		<Quote>"The penalty good men pay for indifference to public affairs is to be ruled by evil men." --Plato</Quote>
		<Quote>"The Bible tells us to love our neighbors, and also to love our enemies; probably because they are generally the same people." --G. K. Chesterton</Quote>
		<Quote>"No one has a finer command of language than the person who keeps his mouth shut." --Sam Rayburn</Quote>
		<Quote>"Civilization is a limitless multiplication of unnecessary necessaries." --Mark Twain</Quote>
		<Quote>"[I]n this battle against fundamentalist Islam, I am hardly preoccupied with political correctness, or who may or may not be offended. Indeed, al-Qa'ida cares little if the Western world is 'offended' by televised images of hostages beheaded in Iraq, subway bombings in London, train attacks in Madrid, or Americans jumping to their death from the Twin Towers as they collapsed. ... As long as this war goes on, being 'offended' should be the least of anyone's worries." --Rep. Tom Tancredo</Quote>
		<Quote>"Congress cannot grasp the idea that anything might conceivably be none of their business. Congressional meddling tends to be short on humility and long on hypocrisy." --Alan Reynolds</Quote>
		<Quote>"As eugenics passes through each of its stages -- from sterilizing the enfeebled at the beginning of the 20th century to aborting the disabled at the end of it and the beginning of the 21st -- man is indeed playing God but without any of His providence or care." --George Neumayr</Quote>
		<Quote>"Faith declares what the senses do not see, but not the contrary of what they see.  It is above them, not contrary to them." --Blaise Pascal</Quote>
		<Quote>"Always retain the old, unchanging truth that happiness is not created by wealth and luxury, but by simplicity, moderation, a pure heart and a peaceful disposition." --Frederick J. Miller</Quote>
		<Quote>"Liberty must at all hazards be supported. We have a right to it, derived from our Maker. But if we had not, our fathers have earned and bought it for us, at the expense of their ease, their estates, their pleasure, and their blood." --John Adams</Quote>
		<Quote>"The sword of Muhammad and the Quran are the most fatal enemies of civilization, liberty and truth which the world has yet known." --Sir William Muir</Quote>
		<Quote>"The shortest and surest way to live with honor in the world is to be in reality what we would appear to be." --Socrates</Quote>
		<Quote>"I am for doing good to the poor, but...I think the best way of doing good to the poor, is not making them easy in poverty, but leading or driving them out of it." --Benjamin Franklin</Quote>
		<Quote>"Experience teaches us to be most on our guard to protect liberty when the government's purpose is beneficent." --Supreme Court Justice Louis Brandeis</Quote>
		<Quote>"Great is the road I climb, but the garland offered by an easier effort is not worth the gathering." --Sextus Propertius</Quote>
		<Quote>"Nothing arouses ambition so much...as the trumpet clang of another's fame." --Baltasar Gracian</Quote>
		<Quote>"The efforts which we make to escape from our destiny only serve to lead us into it." --Ralph Waldo Emerson</Quote>
		<Quote>"I cannot find any authority in the Constitution for public charity. [To approve such spending] would be contrary to the letter and the spirit of the Constitution and subversive to the whole theory upon which the Union of these States is founded." --President Franklin Pierce</Quote>
		<Quote>"If the present Congress errs in too much talking, how can it be otherwise in a body to which the people send 150 lawyers, whose trade it is to question everything, yield nothing, and talk by the hour?" --Thomas Jefferson</Quote>
		<Quote>"Consider the lilies how they grow: they toil not, they spin not; and yet I say unto you, that Solomon in all his glory was not arrayed like one of these." --Jesus Christ</Quote>
		<Quote>It is by caffeine alone I set my mind in motion.  It is by the beans of java that the thoughts acquire speed, the hands acquire shaking, the shaking becomes a warning.  It is by caffeine alone I set my mind in motion.</Quote>
		<Quote>Beauty is in the eye of the beerholder.</Quote>
		<Quote>"Posterity -- you will never know how much it has cost my generation to preserve your freedom. I hope you will make  good use of it." --John Quincy Adams</Quote>
		<Quote>"Citizens by birth or choice of a common country, that country has a right to concentrate your affections. The name of American, which belongs to you, in your national capacity, must always exalt the just pride of Patriotism, more than any appellation derived from local discriminations." --George Washington</Quote>
		<Quote>"The essential characteristic of Western civilization that distinguishes it from the arrested and petrified civilizations of the East was and is its concern for freedom from the state." --Ludwig Von Mises</Quote>
		<Quote>"A life spent making mistakes is not only more honorable, but more useful than a life spent doing nothing." --George Bernard Shaw</Quote>
		<Quote>"Death is not the end. There remains the litigation over the estate." --Ambrose Bierce</Quote>
	</Quotes>
</Signature>