<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Signature>
	<Separator>--</Separator>
	<Name>Your Name</Name>
	<NickName>A nickname or other that you might want to append.</NickName>
	<OtherInfo>other info that doesn't really fit elsewhere.</OtherInfo>
	<Email>bjohns@greendragonweb.com</Email>
	<Phone></Phone>
	<WebPage>Your website if you want it to show up in your signature.</WebPage>
	<Boilerplate>If you're one of those who likes, or is required, to put a legalese statement in your emails put it here.</Boilerplate>
	<Quotes>
		<Quote>"First they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they attack you, and then you win!" --Ghandi</Quote>
		<Quote>"If you can keep your wits about you while all others are losing theirs and blaming you... The world will be yours and everything in it, what's more, you'll be a man, my son." --Rudyard Kipling</Quote>
		<Quote>"When you were born, you cried and the world rejoiced. Live your life so that when you die, the world cries and you rejoice."  --Cherokee Expression</Quote>
		<Quote>"Who is more irrational? A man who believes in a God he doesn't see, or a man who's offended by a God he doesn't believe in?" --Brad Stine</Quote>
		<Quote>"One can pay back the loan of gold, but one dies forever in debt to those who are kind." --Malayan Proverb</Quote>
		<Quote>"What experience and history teach is this:  that people and governments never have learned anything from history, or acted on principles deduced from it." --Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel</Quote>
		<Quote>"It is dangerous to be right in matters on which the established authorities are wrong." --Voltaire</Quote>
		<Quote>"The unforgivable crime is soft hitting. Do not hit at all if it can be avoided; but never hit softly." --Theodore Roosevelt</Quote>
		<Quote>
			while(!Caffeine == null) {
			WriteCode();
			}
		</Quote>
		<Quote>
			^                       ^
			|\   \        /        /|
			/  \  |\__  __/|       /  \
			/ /\ \ \ _ \/ _ /      /    \
			/ / /\ \ {*}\/{*}      /  / \ \
			| | | \ \( (00) )     /  // |\ \
			| | | |\ \(V""V)\    /  / | || \|
			| | | | \ |^--^| \  /  / || || ||
			/ / /  | |( WWWW__ \/  /| || || ||
			| | | | | |  \______\  / / || || ||
			| | | / | | )|______\ ) | / | || ||
			/ / /  / /  /______/   /| \ \ || ||
			/ / /  / /  /\_____/  |/ /__\ \ \ \ \
			| | | / /  /\______/    \   \__| \ \ \
			| | | | | |\______ __    \_    \__|_| \
			| | ,___ /\______ _  _     \_       \  |
			| |/    /\_____  /    \      \__     \ |    /\
			|/ |   |\______ |      |        \___  \ |__/  \
			v  |   |\______ |      |            \___/     |
			|   |\______ |      |                    __/
			\   \________\_    _\               ____/
			__/   /\_____ __/   /   )\_,      _____/
			/  ___/  \uuuu/  ___/___)    \______/
			VVV  V        VVV  V
		</Quote>
		<Quote>"It's as easy as 01 10 11."</Quote>
		<Quote>"There are 10 kinds of people in the world.  Those who understand binary and those who don't."</Quote>
		<Quote>It is by caffeine alone I set my mind in motion.  It is by the beans of java that the thoughts acquire speed, the hands acquire shaking, the shaking becomes a warning.  It is by caffeine alone I set my mind in motion.</Quote>
		<Quote>Beauty is in the eye of the beerholder.</Quote>
		<Quote>"A life spent making mistakes is not only more honorable, but more useful than a life spent doing nothing." --George Bernard Shaw</Quote>
		<Quote>"Death is not the end. There remains the litigation over the estate." --Ambrose Bierce</Quote>
	</Quotes>
</Signature>